[{"answer": "my friend and I used to be like tha", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " You think maybe she's mad cause I haven't asked her to move in", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Why? What's going on", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": " What kind of doctor's appointment", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What kind", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "I don't know", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Well I do know, but I can't pronounce it. Neuroscharnoma or something", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " What is he saying", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Cancer? What do you mean you have cancer", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": " I have cancer", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "I", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I don't believe it. Why can't he just get a latte like he does every morning", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "No we don't have plenty of time! Life is finite", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "What do you mean who", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "my friend and my friend...The doctors found it", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Alright. Fine, we can keep the dog", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Really", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Ah, okay", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Like a specific kind of green food", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " What", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I love you", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "What about those seats up there in the front", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Please. My son has cancer", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I was just injected with three pints of kryptonite. Can we please hold off on the new agey stuff", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What I need is for people to stop telling me what I need", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": " I hope I'm not interrupting. 78", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": " This is your therapist", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": " I'm not just some car service here to shuttle you around", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "And what is it that I'm not taking responsibility for", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": " Yeah, look at you", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": " You want to come back? Here", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Don't be like that. I didn't do anything wrong", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "my friend you're being ridiculous", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " You've been cheating on me", "docId": "50-50.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Am I", "qsentId": 36}]